ifp3.com 2008-12-19

# ifp3 - Photography Web Sites - Privacy Policy

This is the Privacy Policy for ifp3. This Privacy Policy was created to advise you of information gathering and distribution practices of ifp3. 

The entirety of this website is a subsidiary of and is owned and operated by i-magination.net, LLC, and is protected by copyright and the intellectual property laws of the United States and the Berne Convention. This includes but is not limited to text, design, animation, content, images, graphics, and code. No part of this website may be copied or retransmitted.

In order to get full use of the ifp3 demo you will need to register with the website. This requires you to give your e-mail, a password, your full name, and city of birth. A cookie will be placed on your computer for verification purposes. No other information is stored on your computer. The cookie is used to identify you when you return to ifp3 and allows you to visit the website without having to log on each time. ifp3 uses this information to hold your site use information (i.e. pictures held in the light box) on our server. Cookies can only be read by the website that placed them. If you periodically erase your cookies or have not visited for more than 90 days you may have to log on when you return to ifp3. We do not use cookies to examine your surfing behavior before or after visiting this website.

Providing information online is always voluntary, and you are free to decline from completing registration or transactions. If you choose not to provide requested information, however, some products and services may not be available to you.

We may from time to time contact you via e-mail to confirm an order or in the case of a purchasing issue. Your information may be used to advise you of specials and/or upgrades to the ifp3 website. We do not share, give, or sell your personal information, including your mailing address, to any third parties.

If you give us your phone number we will call you only if it directly relates to ongoing business between you and ifp3. We will not call with any solicitation or promotion even if it does directly relate to business between you and ifp3. Any such promotions may be sent to you via e-mail or through the regular mail. If you do not want to receive information on specials or promotions you may choose to opt out.

All financial transactions are preformed through SSL (Secure Socket Layers.)

If you need to update your user information please contact us via e-mail. Please include your old and new information.

We reserve the right to disclose your contact or order information if required to do so by law.

ifp3 reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. All revisions will be posted on this website.

© 2006 ifp3.com. All rights reserved. Privacy Policy.

All images and content of this website are owned by ifp3.
